The search for her son was over. The search for her family was just beginning.
The Deep End of the Ocean is a drama, mystery film directed by Ulu Grosbard.
A three-year-old boy disappears during his mother's high school reunion.
Nine years later, by chance, he turns up in the town in
which the family has just relocated.
Beth Cappadora, played by Michelle Pfeiffer.
Pat Cappadora, played by Treat Williams.
Vincent Cappadora  (age 16), played by Jonathan Jackson.
Sam Karras, played by Ryan Merriman.
Kerry Cappadora (age 9), played by Alexa PenaVega.
Candy Bliss, played by Whoopi Goldberg.
The Deep End of the Ocean is a 1999 American drama film directed by Ulu Grosbard, and starring
Michelle Pfeiffer, Treat Williams, Jonathan Jackson, John Kapelos, and Whoopi Goldberg.
It is based on the 1996 novel by Jacquelyn Mitchard, a bestseller that was the first novel
selected by Oprah Winfrey to be discussed on Oprah's Book Club in 1996.
The film tells the story of a family's reaction when Ben, the youngest son, is kidnapped and then
found nine years later, living in the same town where his family had just moved.
The film was released in theaters on March 12, 1999, by Columbia Pictures,
and was a box-office flop, grossing $28 million worldwide.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.